This is all is our spaceship!
Ross128, our heart the
star Sun это Солн©Э€ у которого есть
Коль©А. and we moving in our trip all
the time. it's like a вА₽Пйøн
engine. barionic engine. great
starboard. and our lovers:_
she became a stargate! when
she born a child and we
keep our journey after life
and our mind is recorded to the
Yttre_staхон. RymdStation [pÅ svenska]; and
it's a very interesting
theorys I find out and first so
called stargonavt was King Tamar
from Georgia it's about a ©Книга and
it's a long story. on ჼOlД Svalbardian
gamle SvalbardiAჼ'. and you call
it Sumeruli or Sumerian but it's
actually the $'imeruli it's a
finance it from the dollar first
signe $ [dÅ] and after it's p [₽]
is from the Ruble and star journey is in a nebula
or ღ₽убЛьЭ€ბი and it's quite complicated
to learn this wordiguჼal
of languages: like physics,
like chemistry, Kemi, ღRublia, and
ჼAurörA b@rჯღaljus [Aurora Borjaljusი]
it's our [vår vatten bargos]
and I do some machine which
will made from light water. and
keep walking on this direction
with levitation and teleportation of ÄÅ
micro particles. at first ... but planet
needs water, it's most stuff
water and we need to create
this gerrätte. and all these
binar journey it's like a
music we are like music creatures:
МО©იКАн²ტ. and my grandfather he was
a guinecologist and his wife too. I knew she was
from ღRublia or რაშა [ნაშა uз Russia] how
you say. but I find out
when I journey she was
from Dannemar©k or bar_dan_ger. and they
unified ჼЭЛrazia. and he made JÅrön = JÅ₽an
like you say. but
dominant financy
a Ruble like you say, also like you
see and JÅr and it's heracloglyphs like
Heracles; it's very interesting
they can't directly send to
us text but it shows by
huge hysterricål stories
that what should we keep to do or
I'm sure human gen or my own
bargen it's possible if
I should lived იn a Japიn
on a high building skiskrappan, there I
could create my seismologic gen and I could
say before of Erdbeben, Earthqueic
that is going to happen! but it's
pretty much water runaway and
I have too much paid friends
they all are paid for just be
a friend or to ter relatives:
ნათესლავები, but they need also updates every
49 years because it happens automatically
on yttrestation! and we can't
change anything! we just can love
each other and united ₽ower ...
Aurora is the name
of this singer.
Aurora Aksens [ახსენებს, аксенебс] like this old
sumerian or Dimeruli $ime₽uli.
It's like she gave me to remember.
And I all my life looking for my tvilling her it.
And because we not journey alone.
Mostly in our family, but with our
lover, with our favourite or partner.
Partnerinna.
But here is people understood two well
stages. Because every my cousinnas = barcousinas
are somehow my ex favoritas too. its about
peast lives. because my grandfather is me
and she [mitt tvilling syskon, schwester] was
my grandmother. they was in love. and like
a uncles & tantes like ჼinibarsity, ჼuniвæ₽©ity
университётი. it's about a imunity, იმუნიტეტი,
©iMoneteTTი. and I create it! but I know there
is too lazy journalistKA, to lazy histeri©ans
or sciensists. that seems they pray to some
great figures, keep some social
hel₽, but bar'° bar10 ბარათი,
[бараты = bara du]. Car like a ©A₽ [ЦАРЬ], so,
it will be never finnisched! I have go now!